Guide to the Situationist Collection, 1957-2005.
Situationist Collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Situationist Collection, 1957-2005.
8111
Kugelberg, Johan,
3.5
Printed materials, artwork, and photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
A collection of rare printed materials, artwork and other images documenting the ideas and influence of the Situationist International.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Situationist International (SI) was an international organization of social revolutionaries made up of avant-garde artists, intellectuals, and political theorists, prominent in Europe from its formation in 1957 to its dissolution in 1972.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
A collection of rare printed materials, artwork and other images documenting the ideas and influence of the Situationist International. Material includes 291 publications (70 books; 195 zines, pamphlets, and periodicals; 25 exhibit catalogs), 84 fliers & handbills, posters & stickers, 4 pieces of original artwork, 3 photographs, 4 prints, approximately 100 leaves of photocopied materials.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kugelberg, Johan,; Debord, Guy, 1931-1994.; Jorn, Asger, 1914-1973; Nash, Jørgen; Reid, Jamie; Internationale situationniste.
Subjects:
Political theory.; Avant garde.; Arts -- Experimental methods.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Publications
Boxes 1-5
Zines, Pamphlets, Periodicals
Exhibit Catalogs
Photocopies and Articles
Series II. Ephemera
Box 3
Series III. Artwork
Box 3-5, Mapcase Folders 1-2
Prints and Painting
Broadsides and Posters
Photographs
CONTAINER LIST
- Publications
  - Zines, Pamphlets, Periodicals
    Alphabetical by name of Publication
    - Anarchist Booklist, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Libertarian Bookclub
    - Anarchist Parenting: An Anarchist FAQ, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Norfolk: Unite Resist Reclaim Literature Collective
    - Anarchistisches Manifest, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Verlag Buchse der Pandora
    - The Angry Brigade, June 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Bratach Dubh Documents No. 1
    - Arkitekten: Ugehæfte, No. 16-17, April 1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - At Dusk: The Situationist Movement In Historical Perspective, January 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Copy Cats (First published in August 1975)
    - Authoritarian Conditioning, Sexual Repression, and the Irrational in Politics, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Solidarity Pamphlet No. 33 (last date noted: 1967)
    - Beyond Automation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
      George & Louise Crowley; first appeared in Monthly Review magazine, reprinted in Anarchy magazine
    - Black & Red, No. 3, November 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - The Black Flag Anarcho-Quiz Book, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Compiled by Albert Meltzer; first published in 1976 by Simian Publications
    - Black Book Politcal Police in Britain, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
      PIG Publication
    - Buffo!: Amazing Tales of Political Pranks and Anarchic Buffoonery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Spectacular Times
    - Build the Anti-Imperialist Student Movement, Augst 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      The Revolutionary Union
    - Bureau of Public Secrets, January 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      No. 1; Editor Ken Knabb; Berkeley: Bureau of Public Secrets
    - Cahiers D'Etudes Anarchistes, November 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      No. 41, 42 on cover No. 42, 43 inside; Black & Red(Noir et Rouge)
    - The Call, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
      The Invisible Committee; Black Powder Press
    - Cambridge Warp, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
      No. 2; St. Valentine's Day Massacre Issue
    - Carry on Consciousness, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The Catalyst Times, July 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      The Guerrilla Press
    - Ceylon: the JVP Uprising of April 1971, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Solidarity
    - CFC: A weekly Communication to the People, May 14, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Vol. 1, No. 1; CFC Communications Section
    - CFC: A weekly Communication to the People, May 21 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Vol. 1, No. 2; CFC Communications Section
    - CFC: A weekly Communication to the People, May 28, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Vol. 1, No. 3; CFC Communications Section
    - CFC: A weekly Communication to the People, June 11, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Vol. 1, No. 5; CFC Communications Section
    - the consul, August 15, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Ralph Rumney; translated from French by Malcolm Imrie; San Francisco: City Light Books
    - The Crisis of the Gross National Spectacle, January 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Robert Cooperstein
    - A Critique of Stewart Home, Art and The Adolf Hitler Fan Club, October 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Poison Pawn Publications; copies 2
    - The Decline and the Fall of the Spectacular Commodity-Economy, September 1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Solidarity Communications
    - The Decline and the Fall of the Spectacular Commodity-Economy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Frontier Press
    - Delftse School, No. 3, March 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Den Anarkistiska Verksamheten Under Revolutionstider, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Peter Krapotkin; Stockholm: Bokförlaget Brand
    - Den Ryska Revoltionen: Och Vad Vi Skola Lära Därav, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Olof Aschberg; Stockholm
    - Desire and Need, August 1967 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Murray Bookchim; New York: Black Flag Anarchists
    - Det Naturlige Smil af Jorgen Nash, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Note inside cover
    - Dialectics of Black Power, January 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Robert L. Allen
    - Disinterest Compounded Daily: A Critique of Point-Blank A a Revolutionary Organization and a Few Proposals for the Supersession of Situationism, February 1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Gina Rosenberg & Chris Shutes
    - Disinterst Compounded Daily, December 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Gina Rosenberg & Chris Shutes; third printing; Berkeley
    - Disputations: On Art, Anarchy and Assholism, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Stewart Home; London: Sabotage Editions
    - Dit hap-hap-happens in Amsterdam, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Cor Jaring's pictures, Henk J. Meier's text, and Jacques Teljeur's layout; The Magic Center Amsterdam
    - Diversion, June 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      No. 1; Brooklyn
    - Double Relfection: Preface to a Phenomenology of the Subjective Aspect of Practical-Critical Activity, May 1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      Ken Knabb; London: Spontaneous Combustion; Berkeley: Bureau of Public Secrets; copies 3
    - Drakabygget, March 1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      No. 1; Complete run
    - Drakabygget, November 1962 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      No. 2-3; Complete run
    - Drakabygget, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      No. 4-5; Complete run
    - Drakabygget, March 19, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      No. 6-8; Complete run
    - Drakabygget, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      No. 9-11; Complete run
    - Drawings, Poems, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      Gordon Fazakerley; Bauhaus Situationniste; includes mimeo-graphed mass-mailed letter addressed to Per Bergman
    - Embryo, No. 4, January/February 1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - The FETISH Speaks!, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      Detroit: Black & Red; First published January 1969
    - Fiction de la Contestation Aliénée, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Hubert Tonka; Editor J. J. Pauvert
    - A Field Study in the Dwindling Force of Cognition, Where it is Least Expected: A Critique of the Situationist International as a Revolutionary Organization, February - March 1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      Robert Chasse & Bruce Elwell
    - Finns det Politisk Musik?, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      Boras
    - Gas, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - The German Guerrilla: Terror, Reaction, and Resistance, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Cienfuegos Press & Soil of Liberty
    - Guy Debord Is Really Dead, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      Luther Blissett; London: Sabotage Editions
    - How to Read Donald Duck: Imperialist Ideology in the Disney Comic, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      Ariel Dorfman & Armand Mattelart; transl. David Kunzle; originally published Chile, IG Editions Inc. in US
    - The Human Condition & Beyond, 1967, August 1967 (Box 1, Folder 53)
      Bruce Elwell; New York: Anarchos
    - Hungary 56, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 54)
      Andy Anderson; Solidarity
    - Idiot International, April 1970 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      No. 4; London: Idiot International Publications
    - The Incoherence of the Intellectual, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      Black & Red
    - Instead of A Magazine, Summer - Fall 1986 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      Vol. 6 No. 39, 40; Lysander Spooner Society
    - International Blacklist: An Anti-authoritarian Directory, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Italy: New Tactics and Organization, Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
      Vol. 1 No. 1; International Workers Solidarity Committee
    - Kapitalism och Kommunism, October 1974 (Box 1, Folder 60)
      Jean Barrot; Stockholm
    - Kim Il Sung, Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
      Report at the 20th Anniversary Celebration of the Founding of the D.P.R.K. given on September 7, 1968
    - Konkret, No. 6, September 1968 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - La F.A. et Les Situationnistes, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Laissez Faire Books: Anarchist Catalog, October 1974 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Laissez Faire Books: Catalog & Review, March 1977 (Box 1, Folder 64)
      New York - 5th Anniversary Edition (11th Edition overall)
    - Laissez Faire Books: Libertarian Catalog, November 1974 (Box 1, Folder 65)
      Fifth edition
    - Land and Liberation: A Brief Introduction to Radical Terrorism, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Las Cárceles y su Influencia Moral Sobre Las Presas, Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
      Pedro Kropotkin
    - L'Autogestion L'Etat et la Revolution, May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 68)
      Supplemental No. 41; Black & Red(Noir et Rouge)
    - Leaving the 20th Century, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 69)
      Translated & edited by Christopher Gray; Free Fall Publications
    - Leisure, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Les Luttes de Classes, No. 1, October 1967 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Libertarian Analysis, Vol. 1, No. 4, December 22, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Lichtspuren Flugschrift, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Lip and the Self-Managed Counter-Revolution, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 73)
      Originally published in Negation No. 3; translated from French by Peter Rachleff & Alan Wallach; Detroit: Black & Red
    - Literature & Ideology, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 74)
      No. 10, 11; Progressive Books & Periodicals
    - Littérature, October 2007 (Box 1, Folder 75)
      No. 6; Paris: Librairie J.-F. Fourcade
    - The Little Red Struggler: A Handbook For Student Militants, Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
      National Student Committee of the Communist Party
    - Live It! Communalism, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 77)
      Vocations for Social Change
    - L'Obscurité du Moment Non-Vécu, Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - London Psychogeography: Rachman Riots and Rillington Place, Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
      Tom Vague
    - Manual For Revolutionary Leaders, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Masses & Mainstream, Vol. 6, No. 8, August 1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, July 11, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Maurice Lemaître; copyright 1966
    - Methods for the Communication of Confusion, August 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Berkeley: Contradiction
    - Minimanueal of the Urban Guerrilla, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      New World Liberation Front
    - The Minimum Definition of Intelligence: Theses On the Construction of One's Own Self-Theory, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Minutemen: America's Last Line of Defence Against Communism, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Minutemen
    - Miserable Publicity: A Disinterested Response, March 17, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Berkeley: Point-Blank!
    - The Misery of Football considered in all its forms, and a few remedies offered, January 5, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      F. A. Kicker; First published March 10, 1995
    - The Misery of Islam, March 2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Al-Djouhall; One Thousand Emotions, first published by Fast Camel Press, Feb. 1989
    - Modern Citizen: School's Out-Forever!, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Detroit: The Urbane Gorilla
    - Modifications, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      (last date noted: May 1959)
    - Neon Lights, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Moss Side Press Ltd. (circa 1970s)
    - Neon Meat-Dream, December 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Cambridge; End-of-term issue
    - New Babylon, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Den Haag: Haags Gemeentemuseum
    - Not Bored!, January 1987 - June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      No. 11, 12, 14, 18, 19
    - Not Bored!, September 20, 1995 - May 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      No. 24, 27, 28, 34, 36, 37
    - Nothing to Declare: A scene from an exile's chronicle, June 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Mike Thomas; London: BOZO
    - October 79, Winter 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      October Magazine, Ltd.; MIT Press
    - On the Poverty of Berkleley Life and the Marginal Stratum of American Society in General, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Chris Shutes; Berkeley
    - Organ: För Frihetlig Socialism, No. 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Organizing for Revolution: Documents from the Italian Revolutionary Movement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
      No. 1; East End Backyard Press
    - The Origins of the Anarchist Movement in China, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      reprint by Solidarity - Chicago
    - The Origins of the Movement for Workers Councils, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
      first published in English by Coptic Press in 1968; published by Workers Voices
    - The Oxford Companion to Absolute Freedom, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Phenomenology of the Subjective Aspect of Practical-Critical Activity: Chapter 1: Behindism, December 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Chris Shutes
    - Poèms et Musique Lettristes, August 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Maurice Lemaître; No. 24, includes three 7" vinyl records
    - Point-Blank!, October 1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      No. 1; Berkeley
    - Police! Ouvrez..., August 4, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Paris
    - Political and Armed Struggle, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
      The Palestine National Liberation Movement, Fateh (last date noted: 1968)
    - The Poor & The Superpoor, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
      New York: Create Situations; first published October 1967; (last date noted: 1971)
    - Portugal In Revolt, August 1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      Pathfinder Press
    - Provonography, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Mimeograph Provo broadside
    - Puerto Rico: "Island Paradise" of U.S. Imperialism, February 1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      New Outlook Publishers
    - Radical America, January-February, 1971, September-October 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Vol. 5, No. 1, 5; Monthly Review Press; copies 2 of No. 1
    - Radical America, Vol. 6, No. 1, May-June 1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Re-Fuse: Further Dialectical Adventures into the (Un)known, September 1978 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      London: Nick Brandt, B.M. Combustion
    - Remarks on Contradiction and its Failure, March 1973 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Ken Knabb; Berkeley: Bureau of Public Secrets; includes second printing December 1974
    - Report No. 1, December 1974 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Isaac Cronin; Second printing
    - Repression in Argentina: The Violence of Those at the Top, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Canadian Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners
    - The Reproduction of Daily Life, 1969, 1972, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      Fredy Perlman; Detroit: Black & Red; includes original, 1972 reprint, and 1982 reprint by Brisbane: Brickburner Press
    - Revolt in Socialist Yugoslavia, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Black & Red (First printed in 1969 with the title "Birth of a Revolutionary Movement in Yugoslavia")
    - Revolution Until Victory, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
      The Palestine National Liberation Movement, Fateh (last date noted: 1970)
    - Revolutionary Committees as a Method of Organization, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
      San Francisco: More to Come
    - Revolutionary Movement in Yugoslavia, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Revolutionary Theory For Beginners (Pure & Applied), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      (published) Nick Brandt, B.M. Combustion; (printed) Islington Community Press
    - The Revolution of Modern Art and the Modern Art of Revolution, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
      The Boomerang Series No. 3; Chronos Publications; first published October 1994
    - The Right to be Greedy: Theses On The Practical Necessity Of Demanding Everything, February 16, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      FOR OURSELVES Council for Generalized Self-Management
    - Rosa Luxembourg: A Study by Tony Cliff, April 1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      International Socialism (published); Socialist Review Pub. Co. Ltd. (printed)
    - Rumble in the Jungle: Fighting for Freedom in West Papua, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
      No. 8; Solidarity South Pacific
    - Securicor, the State, and Others: Who Is In Control?, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Seige of State (Firing point-blank at San Francisco), Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
      San Francisco: Point-Blank!
    - The Sheep Will Reveal Their Fangs…, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
      Dublin: New Earth; includes articles "An everyman's guide to hell," "The real struggle in the north," "Suggestions concerning the transformation of the existing world"; (last date noted: November 1972)
    - Situationisterne Drakabygget, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
      Sammenslutningen af Danske Kunstforeninger
    - Situationistisk Revolution, No. 1, October 1962 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Skirmishes with an Untimely Man: a Critique of Diversion, January 1975 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      Chris Schutes & Isaac Cronin; first published May 1974
    - Smile, Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
      Issue 2; Anti-Authoritarians Anonymous
    - Smile, Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
      Issue 9
    - Smile, Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
      Issue 10; Bedlam Press
    - The Society of Situationism & Notes Towards a Situationist Manifesto, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
      London: Spontaneous Combustion
    - The Society of the Spectacle, Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
      Guy Debord
    - Society of the Spectacle, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      Guy Debord; unauthorized first English edition; Detroit: Black & Red
    - The Solidarity Catalog of Anarchist Literature, May 1973 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      Chicago: Solidarity
    - Some Facts and Questions that Will No Doubt Convince you to Join the Growing Effort to Stop OPTO, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 61)
      first published November 1996, corrected reprint December 1996
    - Some Notes on the Reproduction of Human Capital, April 1974 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - SPUR, No. 1-4, 6, August 1960 - August 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - Stavrim, Sonetter, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      2nd edition; Copenhagen
    - Strange Defeat: The Chilean Revolution 1973, October 1973 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - The Storm!: A Journal For Free Spirits, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      No. 7; Anarchist Publishers: Cienfuegos Press
    - The Storm!: A Journal For Free Spirits, Undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
      (last date noted: 1979)
    - Student Revolts: The New Left in West Germany, June 2, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      F.C. Hunnius; London: War Resisters' International
    - Sub, Winter 1970 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      Vol. 1, No. 1; Japan
    - Sub, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      Vol. 1, No. 2
    - Sub, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      Vol. 1, No. 3
    - Sur le passage de quelques personnes à travers une assez courte unité de temps, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Take a Pill…The drug industry - private or public?, October 1972 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      Marxists in Medicine
    - Take Over the City, Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Terrorism and Politics in West Germany, Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Theory of Misery / Misery of Theory: Report on the new conditions of revolutionary theory, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      Daniel Denevert; Paris; English translation published September 1974
    - Threads in the Black Flag, Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
      Bibliographic information on anarchism
    - Time Recaptured: Self-Management and the Lip Occupation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Turin 1920: Factory Grounds and General Strike, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      Moulinavent Press
    - Two Local Chapters in the Spectacle of Decomposition, May 1979 (Box 2, Folder 79)
      Chris Shutes; includes poster of chpt 2 "The Death of Harvey Milk"; Berkeley
    - U: Inter-University and College Magazine, Vol. 3 No. 10, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - The Veritable Split in the International Public Circular of the Situationist International, July 1974 (Box 2, Folder 81)
      Originally printed in French in 1972; includes September 1974 print
    - Views & Comments of the Libertarian League, June 1962; Winter 1965 (Box 2, Folder 82)
      No. 43; No. 48; New York: Libertarian Candidate
    - Vrijheid Van Drukpers?: Wat Let Je!, Undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - The Wandering of Humanity, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 84)
      Jacques Camatte; Detroit: Black & Red
    - War-making by Machine, Undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
      National Peace Literature Service
    - The Watts Riot, 1965: The Decline and Fall of the Spectacle-Commodity Economy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
      Last Word Press (from the Situationist International, December 1965)
    - Watts Uprising '65, December 1965 (Box 2, Folder 87)
      Situationist International
    - "We Called a Strike and No One Came", Christmas 1968 (Box 2, Folder 88)
      No. 4; Detroit: Black & Red; includes original & 1973 reprint
    - Who Says You Can't Fight City Hall?, January 13, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 89)
      Constitutional Revival
    - Wildcat Comics, Undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
      Berkeley: For the Situationist Project; appraisal of item included
    - Wildcat: Dodge Truck, June 1974 (Box 2, Folder 91)
      Detroit: Black & Red
    - Worker-Student Action Committees: France, May '68, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Working Papers in European Criminology: Terrorism and the Violence of the State, September 1979 (Box 2, Folder 93)
      No. 1; European Group for the Study of Deviance and Social Control
    - World Labor Needs a Union, November 1969 (Box 2, Folder 94)
      Fred Thompson; Chicago: Industrial Workers of the World
    - World Law vs. World Anarchy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
      Owen J. Roberts; reprinted by the Atlantic Union Committee
    - You Can't Blow Up a Social Relationship: The Anarchist Case Against Terrorism, December 1985 (Box 2, Folder 96)
      Chaz Bufe; San Francisco: Acrata Press
  - Exhibit Catalogs
    - Accidental Paintings, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Jacqueline de Jong; includes inscription by de Jong
    - Asger Jorn, March 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Catalogue 21; Peter Grosell´s Antikvariat
    - Asger Jorn fotograferet af Borge Venge, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Silkeborg: Galerie Moderne
    - Asger Jorn: Luxury Paintings, May 30 - June 24, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Constant, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Constant, March 4 -April 9, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Stadtische Kunstgalerie exhibit catalgoue
    - Constant, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      H van. Haaren; translated from Dutch by Max Schucart; Amsterdam
    - Constant, November 28, 1974 - January 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Constant, March 17 - May 5, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Schilderijen 1969-77
    - Constant, October 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Haags Gemeente Museum exhibit brochure
    - Constant 1945-'65, February 12 - March 7, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Constant, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Constant, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Fin de Copenhague, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Asger Jorn; edition Allia; originally published in 1957, also includes 2001 print